[
  {
    "id": "001",
    "question_text": "From 0 to 100, what is the chance of rain in Recife below 100mm?",
    "op": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Recife"
    ],
    "answer": 47,
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "002",
    "question_text": "From 0 to 100, what is the chance of rain in the area of Jaboatão dos Guararapes over 100mm?",
    "op": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Jaboatão dos Guararapes"
    ],
    "answer": 42,
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "003",
    "question_text": "From 0 to 100, what is the chance of rain in the area of São Lourenço da Mata between 50 and 150mm?",
    "op": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "São Lourenço da Mata"
    ],
    "answer": 33,
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "004",
    "question_text": "In which of the two cities is most likely to rain less than 100mm?",
    "op": [
      "Ipojuca",
      "Cabo de Santo Agostinho"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Ipojuca",
      "Cabo de Santo Agostinho"
    ],
    "answer": "Ipojuca",
    "distance": "Short",
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "005",
    "question_text": "In which of the two cities is most likely to rain less than 100mm?",
    "op": [
      "Recife",
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Recife",
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "answer": "Santa Cruz",
    "distance": "Long",
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "006",
    "question_text": "In which of the two cities is most likely to rain more than 100mm?",
    "op": [
      "Sanharó",
      "Petrolândia"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Sanharó",
      "Petrolândia"
    ],
    "answer": "Petrolândia",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": "Low",
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "007",
    "question_text": "In which of the two cities is most likely to rain more than 100mm?",
    "op": [
      "Tacaratu",
      "Araripina"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Tacaratu",
      "Araripina"
    ],
    "answer": "Araripina",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": "High",
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "008",
    "question_text": "In which of the two cities is most likely to rain between 50 and 150mm?",
    "op": [
      "Saloá",
      "Pombos"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Saloá",
      "Pombos"
    ],
    "answer": "Pombos",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": "Small"
  },
  {
    "id": "009",
    "question_text": "In which of the two cities is most likely to rain between 50 and 150mm?",
    "op": [
      "Sertânia",
      "Parnamirim"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      "Sertânia",
      "Parnamirim"
    ],
    "answer": "Sertânia",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": "Large"
  },
  {
    "id": "010",
    "question_text": "Type the name of the area that is most likely to rain below 100mm?",
    "op": [
      ""
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "Jatobá",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "011",
    "question_text": "Type the name of the area that is most likely to rain below 100mm?",
    "op": [
      ""
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "Amaraji",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "012",
    "question_text": "What is the average rainfall in the area of Caruaru?",
    "op": [
      ""
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": 50,
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  },
  {
    "id": "013",
    "question_text": "For rainfall from 40 to 150, can you identify any city whose distribution is different from its neighbors? If so, type the city name, if not type 'No'.",
    "op": [
      "Sim",
      "Não"
    ],
    "highlights": [
      ""
    ],
    "answer": "Sim",
    "distance": {},
    "variance": {},
    "size": {}
  }
]